<resources>
    <string name="app_name">KnowGhana</string>

    <!-- Menu Items -->
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="places">Places/Regions</string>
    <string name="hotels">Hotels</string>
    <string name="business">Businesses/Government Institutions</string>
    <string name="attractions">Tourist Attractions</string>

    <!-- Strings for various Regions in Ghana-->
    <string name="greater_accra_region">Greater Accra Region</string>
    <string name="eastern_region">Eastern Region</string>
    <string name="volta_region">Volta Region</string>
    <string name="western_region">Western Region</string>
    <string name="ashanti_region">Ashanti Region</string>
    <string name="brong_ahafo_region">Brong Ahafo Region</string>
    <string name="northern_region">Northern Region</string>
    <string name="upper_west_region">Upper West Region</string>
    <string name="upper_east_region">Upper East Region</string>
    <string name="central_region">Central Region</string>

    <!-- Brief Story about ghana-->
    <string name="briefNarrationGhana">
        Ghana, a country on the West Coast of Africa, is one of the most thriving democracies
        on the continent. It has often been referred to as an "island of peace" in one of the most
        chaotic regions on earth. It shares boundaries with Togo to the east, la Cote d\'Ivoire to
        the west, Burkina Faso to the north and the Gulf of Guinea, to the south.
        A recent discovery of oil in the Gulf of Guinea could make Ghana an important oil producer
        and exporter in the next few years.

The country\'s economy is dominated by agriculture, which employs about 40 percent of the working
        population. Ghana is one of the leading exporters of cocoa in the world.
        It is also a significant exporter of commodities such as gold and lumber.
        A country covering an area of 238,500 square kilometres, Ghana has an estimated
        population of 25,199,609 (July 2013 est.), drawn from more than one hundred ethnic
        groups - each with its own unique language. English, however, is the official language,
        a legacy of British colonial rule.

In 1957, Ghana (formerly known as the Gold Coast) became the first country in sub-Saharan Africa to
        gain independence. After leading the country for nine years,
        the nation\'s founding president, Kwame Nkrumah was overthrown in a coup d\'etat in 1966.
        After Kwame Nkrumah, Ghana was ruled by a series of military despots with intermittent
        experiments with democratic rule, most of which were curtailed by military takeovers.
        The latest and most enduring democratic experiment started in 1992 and it is what has
        gained recognition for Ghana as a leading democracy in Africa.

Ghana has several tourist attractions such as the castles. Most of the major international
        airlines fly into and from the international airport in Accra. Domestic air travel is
        thriving and the country has a vibrant telecommunications sector, with six cellular phone
        operators and several internet service providers.
    </string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>
